gettimely.com 2019-05-21

# Privacy Policy | Timely Salon & Spa Software

## Effective from 25th May 2018.

When signing up for or using Timely you are entrusting Timely with the protection and sensitivity of your information, and that of your customers. This is a responsibility we take very seriously. This document is intended to outline what we collect, how we store it, what we do with it, and what your rights are as it relates to that data.

This privacy policy is intended to apply to individuals or entities who use Timely’s websites, mobile applications, products and services (collectively, “Services”). For the purposes of this Policy, “User”, as the term is used here, refers to an individual or an entity that uses our Services, referred to as “User” or “Users”.

Any reference to Personal Data means any information stored by Timely that could lead to an individual person being identified either directly or indirectly. This may include but is not limited to name, email address, phone number, street or postal address, IP address etc. By registering for Timely you acknowledge the collection, transfer, storage, processing, disclosure and other uses of your information as outlined in this privacy policy.

User Information, being personal information relating to our Users and (where applicable) their businesses. We collect this information so that we can provide our Services to those Users. For the purposes of GDPR in the European Union, we are the ‘data controller’ of this User Information and we collect and store it for the purposes of providing our Services to Users and maintaining records and contact details relating to those Services and Users. This policy sets out how Timely process your information as a User.

Customer Information, being personal information relating to individuals with whom our Users interact (such as customers of their businesses). Users of our Services are solely responsible for establishing policies for and ensuring compliance with all applicable laws and regulations, as well as all privacy policies, agreements or other obligations, relating to the collection of personal information in connection with the use of our Services by individuals with whom our Users interact. We collect information under the direction of our Users, and have no direct relationship with individuals whose personal information we process in connection with the use of our Services. If you are a User providing information (including personal information) about someone else, you must have the legal ability to do so and, if necessary, inform them about how their personal information will be used (as described in this Privacy Policy). If you are an individual who interacts with a User using our Services – for instance if you’re an employee or customer of a business – that User is the controller of your information and you should contact them directly (e.g. – the owner or manager of the business) – for assistance with any requests or questions relating to your personal information.

Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways:

  * To personalize your experience (your information helps us to better respond to your individual needs)
  * To improve our website (we continually strive to improve our website offerings based on the information and feedback we receive from you)
  * To improve customer service (your information helps us to more effectively respond to your customer service requests and support needs)
  * To process transactions
  * Your information, whether public or private, will not be sold, exchanged, transferred, or given to any other company for any reason whatsoever, without your consent, other than for the express purpose of delivering the purchased product or service requested.
  * To send periodic emails
  * The email address you provide may be used to send you information, respond to inquiries, and/or other requests or questions.

We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information when you place an order or enter, submit, or access your personal information.

All supplied sensitive/credit information is transmitted via Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology and then encrypted into our Payment gateway providers database only to be accessible by those authorized with special access rights to such systems, and are required to keep the information confidential.

Yes (Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computers hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the sites or service providers systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information

We use cookies to help us remember that you’ve logged into Timely, understand and save your preferences for future visits and compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interaction so that we can offer better site experiences and tools in the future.

As you browse gettimely.com, advertising cookies will be placed on your computer so that we can understand what you are interested in. Our display advertising partners, then enable us to present you with retargeting advertising on other sites based on your previous interaction with gettimely.com. The techniques our partners employ do not collect personal information such as your name, email address, postal address or telephone number. You can visit this [page](https://app.adroll.com/optout) to opt out of AdRoll and their partners’ targeted advertising.

Timely sends billing information, product information, Service updates and Service notifications to you via email. Our emails will contain clear and obvious instructions describing how you can choose to be removed from any mailing list not essential to the Service. Timely will remove you at your request.

Timely works with a number of third parties and partners who help us provide the Timely service to our Users. Examples include hosting services, accounting services, business intelligence platforms, email and SMS partners, customer relationship management services, customer support platforms and more. In order to supply the Timely service Timely may send them Personal Data for storage or processing. Timely has taken steps to ensure that each partner or third party involved treats the Personal Data in accordance with the privacy laws and legislation of our Users’ jurisdictions.

We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety.

Non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.

Other than stated above, we do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information.

Occasionally, at our discretion, we may include or offer third party products or services on our website. By opting to take up these third party products you agree to Timely providing your information to these third parties and you acknowledge that these third party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites.

To quickly and efficiently resolve customer support issues related to your account, you consent to us logging into your account from time-to-time. If you do not wish us to access your account, then you may notify us in writing.

To bring you Services, we operate globally. In order to do so, your personal information may be transferred to, and processed in countries other than the country you live in, outside of your home country, including to Australia, New Zealand, United Kingdom and the United States. These countries may have laws different to what you’re used to. Rest assured, where we disclose Personal Data to a third party in another country, we put safeguards in place to ensure your Personal Data remains protected.

Specifically, Timely hosts data with Microsoft Azure in the United States and in Australia. This means that your personal information will be transferred to the US or to Australia. The servers on which personal information is stored are kept in a controlled and secure environment.

European Economic Area (EEA) users: This means that your information may be transferred outside of the EEA. Where your personal information is transferred outside the EEA, it will only be transferred to countries that have been deemed to provide adequate protection for EEA information (like New Zealand and Australia), or to a third party where we have approved transfer mechanisms in place to protect your personal information – i.e., by entering into the European Commission’s Standard Contractual Clauses, or by ensuring the entity is Privacy Shield certified (for transfers to US based third parties).

Australian users: The third parties we share data with do not control, and are not permitted to access or use your Personal Data, except for the limited purpose it was provided. This means that, for the purposes of Australian privacy legislation and Australian users, Timely does not disclose Personal Data to third parties located overseas

Deactivating your account

If you wish to deactivate your Timely account, you may do so by logging into your Timely account and following [these instructions](https://help.gettimely.com/article/485-how-to-pause-or-cancel-your-account).

Your European Privacy Rights

In addition to the rights listed above, if you are in the EEA you also have rights to:

  * Know what personal information we hold about you, and to make sure it’s correct and up to date
  * Request a copy of your personal information or ask us to restrict processing of or delete it
  * Object to our continued processing of your personal information and to request a permanent deletion of your data

For more information about your European Privacy Rights, please see our [GDPR help guide](https://help.gettimely.com/article/655-privacy-at-timely-gdpr).

If you’re not happy with how we are processing your personal information, you have the right to complain to your local information protection authority. Your local data protection authority will be able to give you more information on how to submit a complaint.

You can request to exercise these rights by emailing [privacy@gettimely.com](mailto:privacy@gettimely.com). We will process your request within 30 days of receiving your request. Note that we may require proof of identification before we process your request.

Our Services are not directed to children, and you may not use our Services if you are under the age of 18. You must also be old enough to consent to the processing of your Personal Data in your country (in some countries we may allow your parent or guardian to do so on your behalf).

By using our site, you consent to our privacy policy.

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page.
